Will Earth wait for us?
The Colony is a science fiction, thriller film directed by Tim Fehlbaum.
In the not-too-distant future: after a global catastrophe has wiped out nearly all of humanity on Earth, an elite
astronaut from Space Colony Kepler must make a decision that will seal the fate of the people on both planets.
Blake, played by Nora Arnezeder.
Gibson, played by Iain Glen.
Narvik, played by Sarah-Sofie Boussnina.
Tucker, played by Ṣọpẹ́ Dìrísù.
Father, played by Sebastian Roché.
Paling, played by Joel Basman.
Tides (also known as The Colony) is a 2021 English-language science
fiction thriller film directed and written by Tim Fehlbaum.
The film stars Nora Arnezeder, Iain Glen,
Sarah-Sofie Boussnina, and Joel Basman.
Set in a future in which the Earth's elite leave the polluted planet to settle in a space colony on Kepler-209, it is about a
team from Kepler who return to Earth several generations later to test whether it is suitable for human habitation.
The film had its worldwide premiere at the 71st
Berlin International Film Festival.
The film explores themes of dystopia, post-apocalyptic
future, space travel, space, apocalypse.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.